特兰西瓦尼亚
1897年
布达佩斯
Budapest, Budapest,
下一站  布达佩斯
the next stop, Budapest.
下一站布达佩斯
Budapest is the next stop.
布达佩斯
Budapest.
检票了  女士们  给你
Tickets, ladies. Ooh, here you go.
这是我的  我的
Here's mine. And mine.
我的  给你
Mine too. Here you go.
谢谢你  小伙子
And, thank you, young man.
我真讨厌穿成这样
Man, I hate wearing disguises.
这鞋太挤脚了
This heels are killing me.
好了小点声  别让人类发现了
Okay, take it down a notch, we don't want to alarm the humans.
德古拉
Psst, Drac.
我快要疯了
I'm about to want to freak out!
你是只乖猫咪
You're a nice kitty.
我是乖猫咪  喵喵
I'm good kitty cat. Meow, meow.
哦不  又是这个傻逼
Oh, no, not this clown again.
晚上好乘客们  我是亚伯拉罕・范・海辛教授
Good evening, travelers, I am professor Abraham Van Helsing.
没错  来自范・海辛家族
Yes. One of the Van Helsing's.
几百年来
For centuries,
我的家人都在保护人类远离邪恶的怪兽
my families has protected humanity from the evils of monsters.
所以相信我接下来的话
So, you can believe me when I tell you
你们之间藏有怪兽
there are monsters hiding amongst you!
但无需担忧  我可是专业的
But fear not, for I am a professional.
我知道怎么把它引出来
And I know how to flush out these beasts.
将其带到光明之下
And bring them into the light!
火啊  不好
Fire, bad!
抱歉啦  兄弟
Sorry, guys.
没关系  我先杀了你  再来解决他们
Fine, first I kill Dracula, and then the rest of the monsters!
你为啥要这么坚持
Why do you keep doing this?
你爸  你祖父还有曾祖母
Your dad, your grandfather, your greatgreatgranny.
都被我打败了
I defeated them all.
你们范・海辛什么时候才能学会放下呢
When will you Van Helsing's ever learn to let go of the hate?
不可能  因为怪兽生性邪恶
Never! Because you monsters are evil!
吱吱  变老鼠干嘛
Eh, squeak, squeak? Huh, a mouse?
你逃不出我手掌心的  黑暗王子
You can't run from me, Prince of Darkness!
我会永远追杀你的
I will hunt you for all eternity.
我发誓  不毁了你绝不收手
I swear, I will never rest until I destroy you!
还有  其它的  怪兽
And... every... other... monsters...
就算这是  我做的  最后  一件事
If it's the last thing... I... ever... do!
天哪  这哥们真够烦的
Boy, that guy is annoying.
也许某天会有个地方
Maybe one day there will be a place
能够接纳怪兽  远离这一切
where the monsters can go, to get away from it all.
去度个假期  谁知道呢
Take a vacation, who knows?
也许还可以结婚
Maybe even get married.
这样岂不很美好
Wouldn't that be something?
精灵旅社
疯狂假期
现今
嘘  好了  嘘
Shh, okay. Shh, shh.
到底什么时候开始啊
When is this thing starting?
你把它们弄哭了  韦恩
Oh, you made them cry, Wayne.
除了这个小宝贝
Oh, Except this little one.
这是珊妮  她从来不哭
That's Sunny, she doesn't cry.
她咬人
She bites.
这是个特别的时刻  卡尔
This is a very special moment, Carl.
不用多久
Any second,
你美丽的妻子就会走进来的
your beautiful bride is going to walk right down the aisle.
哦不  德古拉  她不会来了
Oh no, Drac. She's not coming.
别担心  有梅维斯陪她
Oh, don't worry. Mavis is with her.
我相信一切尽在掌控
I'm sure everything is under control.
小梅  一切还好吗
Mavie, is everything under control?
还行  就是有点婚前小插曲
Um... yup, just a slight case of prewedding jitters.
没错  一切都好
Yup, everything is fine.
拜托放轻松  露西
Please, try to relax, Lucy.
我把一切都处理好了
I've taken care of everything.
婚礼会很完美的
The wedding is going to be perfect.
我不担心这个  只是我怎么知道这是对的事
It's not that. Just... how do I know I'm doing the right thing?
我知道你的感受
I know just how you feel.
我与强尼结婚那天是我这辈子最棒的一天  但
The day I married Johnny was the best day of my life, but...
我当时特别紧张  肯定没我紧张
I was so nervous. Not as nervous as I was.
你真该看看我爸  他简直紧张到爆
And you should have seen my dad, he was a mess.
那晚我紧张得出不去棺材
I wouldn't get out of my coffin that night.
但他知道这是必然的
But he knew it was meant to be.
你的出身与怪异并不重要
It doesn't matter where you come from, or how different you are.
真爱只有一次
A zing only happens once in your life.
你必须要懂得珍惜
And you have to cherish it.
你说得对  谢谢
You're right! Thank you!
好吧  好的  哦  好吧
All right, okay. Oh, okay.
我愿意
I do.
你听到了吗
Do you hear that?
听到了  我们不是把他锁房里了吗
Yes, I thought we locked him in his room.
是啊
We did!
嗨妈妈  嗨祖父
Hi, mom. Hi, papa!
丹尼斯
Dennis!
叮叮乖极了  我就放它出来了
Tinkles is great, so we let him out.
叮叮坐下
Tinkles, sit!
当初是谁说可以让丹尼斯养狗的
Ugh, whose idea was it to let Dennis have a pup?
你说的吧  好吧
Umm, yours? Okay. Eh...
好吧
eh... right.
可怜的叮叮
Poor Tinkles.
丹尼斯
Dennis?
宝贝  我知道你喜欢叮叮
Look, honey, I know you love Tinkles,
但我们不能把狗狗
but we're not allowed to bring our dogs...
我是说不能把"宠物"到处乱带
uh... uh, I mean our pets everywhere.
知道吗  知道了
Okay? Okay.
我是DJ杰西・强尼
DJ Jessy Johnny in the house.
有请我们的幸福夫妇
It's time to welcome the happy couple.
刺刺夫妇
Mr. And Mrs. Prickles!
新郎新娘邀请各位到舞池里跳舞
The bride and groom, invite everyone to join them on the dance floor.
能否赏脸
Care to dance?
那是她吗  小心哦
Is that her? Ooh, watch out now.
她长得真是恰如其分
She got stitches in all the right places.
她绝不可能是你的亲戚  弗兰克
Okay, there's no way that is related to you, Frank.
她是我的右臂亲戚
Well, she's my right arm's cousin.
现在看出来了
Ah, I see it now.
弗兰克想让我见见你
Frank wanted me to meet you.
我们是远方的臂膀亲戚
We're arm cousins. Twice removed.
没错  也只有他有二头肌
Ah, of course, eh... I do recognize that bicep anyway.
他觉得我俩都是单身
He thought since we're both single,
没准能看对眼  再去约个会
we might hit it off. Maybe go on a date?
约会  好吧  只是
Date? Oh, well, eh... it's just that, eh...
DJ台可是很神圣的
Whoa, DJ's booth is a sacred space!
我喜欢这首歌
Oh! I love this song!
你想跳舞吗  德古拉
Do you want to dance? Dracula?
他去哪了
Oh, where'd he go?
德古拉  德古拉
Dracula! Dracula!
怎么了德古拉  不喜欢她吗
What's the matter, Dracula? You didn't like her?
不是我说  但你也太挑剔了
No offense, but you can't be too picky.
你已经100年没约过会了
You haven't had a date in 100 years.
兄弟们  谢谢关心
Look, guys. I appreciate your concerns,
但感情这事我说了不算
but it's... it's not up to me.
真爱只有一次  我爱过了
You only zing once, and I did.
时代变了  哥们
Times have changed, buddy.
现在  你用手机就能找到真爱
You can even find someone to zing with on your phone now.
什么  真的吗
What? Really?
不不不
Oh, no, no, no.
我太忙了
I'm far too busy.
我还有梅维斯  丹尼斯和酒店等等等
I have Mavis and Dennis and the hotel, and blah blah blah.
你们听见没  他居然说了"等等等"
Um, did you guys hear that? He actually said, "Blah blah blah".
我没说"等等等"
I don't say, "Blah blah blah"!
有什么能帮到您的吗  黑暗之王
What can I help you with, Lord of Darkness?
我想要找真爱
Eh, uh... I'm looking for a zing.
好的  更换铃声
Okay, changing phone ring.
不不  我想要找人约会
No, no, I'm looking for a date.
今天是7月13日星期五
The date is Friday, July 13th.
不不不  我想跟人约会
No, no, no, no. I want to meet someone.
明白  你想要来些点心
Understood. You want to eat dim sum.
你在逗我吗
Are you kidding me right now?
你不明白吗  我想出去约会
Don't you get it? I want to go on a date.
我好孤单
I'm... lonely.
我明白
I understand.
你想吃香肠
You want baloney.
啥  自己看看啊  拜托
What? Look at that there, come on.
眼睛太多
Huh? Too many eyes.
眼睛太少
Too few eyes.
不喜欢触角
Not into tentacles.
发现匹配  不不不
Match found? No, no, no! No, no!
丑话说前头
First things first.
我不喜欢游戏
I'm not into games,
你最好有工作
you'd better have a job,
而且我的猫要喜欢你才行
and my cats have to like you.
哦不  不不不
Oh, hey! No, no! Oh, whoa, no!
爸  梅维斯  你在这干什么
Dad? Oh, Mavis! Oh, what are you doing here?
我正要去检查蜜月套房  听见了点动静
I was just checking on the honeymoon suite and I heard something.
抱歉我的小臭虫
Oh, I'm sorry my little bedbug,
我在  在清理阁楼
I wa... I was just cleaning the attic.
谁在那  你在打电话吗
Who is that? Are you on the phone?
啥  这个吗  我只是
What? This? I was just... eh...
想找个女仆帮我清理
trying to find a maid to help me with the mess.
女仆  你以为你在
A maid?! Who do you think...
谢谢  我会查看你的时间并及时给你回电  再见
Thank you, I'll check your apertures and get back to you. Goodbye!
爸爸  别再瞒着我了
Dad, stop trying to hide it from me?
瞒着谁  什么  我吗
Hide? Who? I mean, what, me?
没错
Yes.
我知道怎么回事
And I know what it is.
真的吗
Uh, really?
你的工作压力太大了
You're stressed out from working too hard.
好吧  对  被你发现了
Oh, okay, yes. You got me, yes.
旅社这么大  没法做到事无巨细
Hey, it's a big hotel, you know? Can't get to everything.
那你呢  你自己也很忙啊
What about you, you are pretty busy yourself.
是啊  虽然我们一起工作的时间更多了
I know. It seems like now that we're working together more,
见面的时间却更少了
we're seeing each other less.
是啊  你说得太对了
Oh, yeah, you're absolutely right.
我工作过度  你也工作过度
I'm working too much, you're working too much.
真该休息休息
We should really take a break.
从现在开始  晚安
Starting right now, nightnight.
我还在呢
I'm still here.
嗨宝贝  准备好  约会了吗
Oh! Hey, honey. You ready for... date night?
没关系的宝贝  你休息吧
Aww... that's okay sweetheart, you rest.
爸爸说得对
You know, dad's right.
我们需要休息
We need a break.
我们要在一起  像个完整的家庭
We need to all be together again. Like a family.
像以前一样
We used to.
你是否工作过度压力山大
Have you overworked and stressed out?
是否需要些家庭时光
Do need some family time?
你是怪兽吗
Are you a monster?
你需要个假期
Then you need a vacation.
怪兽的假期
A monster vacation.
欢迎搭乘妖怪航班
Welcome aboard Gremlin Air.
妖怪航班
住手  给我擦玻璃
Stop it! Clean the glass!
女士们先生们
Ladies and gentlemen,
请将您的注意力转移至机舱前方
please direct your attention to the front of the cabin.
为了您的安全  请解开安全带
For your safety, please, unbuckle your seat belts.
我们很有可能
In the likely event,
会遇到舱内压力骤降
we experience a sun dropping cabin pressure...
我们将为您提供氧气
oxygen will be provided for you.
先生  能替您保管行李吗  好的谢了
Can I stow that for you, sir? All right, thanks.
饮品小食  饮品小食
Beverages, beverages, snacks, beverages,
饮品小食  饮品小食  饮品小食
beverages, beverages, snacks, snacks, snacks, beverages!
喝咖啡吗  好呀
Coffee? That would be lovely.
梅维斯求你了  你这是在折磨我
Mavis, please, you're torturing me!
你知道我讨厌惊喜
You know I hate surprises.
这是好的惊喜
This is a fun surprise.
我知道是好惊喜  就告诉我要去哪
I know fun surprises. Just tell me where we're going.
我们为啥在飞机上
Why are we on the plane?
我们自己能飞的
We can fly, you know?
我年轻时候都坐火车  那才叫档次
Back in my day, people took trains. Now, that's classy.
是啊老爸
Sure, dad,
跟你和伯尼叔叔在高档车厢待40个小时
40 hours in a classic size room with you and uncle Bernie,
到处烟雾缭绕
and his smelly cigars.
争论埃及艳后和纳芙蒂蒂谁更有魅力
Arguing who is more attractive, Cleopatra or Nefertiti.
喔  纳芙蒂蒂  好了爸  谢了
Oh, Nefertiti. Okay dad, thank you.
梅维斯  这真是个惊喜
Mavis, this is such an amazing surprise.
我等不及与我最爱的人共同玩耍了
I can't wait to spend time with the people I love most.
但我求你了  告诉我要去哪
But I beg of you... tell me where we're going!
不  我把一切都处理好了
No, I've taken care of everything.
你不用担心  你最近压力太大了
So, you don't need to worry. You've been so stressed out lately.
是时候放松放松了
It's time for you to relax.
是不是好多了  是啊  太放松了
Well, isn't that better. Ooh yes, so relaxed.
我要去看看那个谁
I'm gonna go check on you know who.
我去上洗手间  马上回来
I'll be right back, I have to go to the bathroom.
你看到了吗
Hey, did you see that?
丹尼斯去洗手间了
Dennis went to the bathroom!
好吧
Uh... okay.
你在哪里
Psst! Hey, where are you?
你在这呀  叮叮
There you are, Tinkles.
别担心  我不会让你单独在家的
Don't worry, we'd never leave you home alone.
好了各位
Okay, folks.
飞机准备降落  您可以在机舱内随意走动
You're free to move around the cabin as we had started our descent.
周末有什么计划吗  内特贝尔
So, any made plans for the weekend, Netbale?
跟平常一样  带孩子去踢足球
Oh, you know, the usual. Gotta take the kids to soccer.
饮品小食  饮品小食
Snacks, beverages, snacks, beverages, snacks...
女士们先生们
Thank you, ladies and gentlemen,
我们已经抵达目的地
we've arrived at our destination,
百慕大三角
The Bermuda Triangle.
欢迎来到百慕大三角
Welcome to The Bermuda Triangle,
在此你将登上终生难遇的怪兽游轮
where you'll embark on a monster cruise of a lifetime.
游轮
A cruise!?
惊喜吧
Surprise!
不不不
Oh, no, no, no!
但它就像是  水上的  酒店
But it's... just like a hotel... on the water.
我只是觉得你需要
I just figured you need
一个远离其他人假期的假期
a vacation to running from everyone else's vacation.
你几乎没出过旅社自从
You've barely been out of the hotel since...
自从妈妈去世
Well, since mom died.
但正好借此机会敞开心扉
But this is a chance to make new room for us.
向我们和丹尼斯
With all of us, with Dennis.
谁把你培养得这么优秀的
Who made you such an amazing daughter?
你
You.
没错  我自豪极了
Hehheh, that's right. What a proud man.
来吧  丹尼索维奇  我们出发吧
Come on, Dennisovich, let's get cruising!
遗产号
欢迎登船
好了  微笑
Okay! Smile.
谢谢
Thank you.
"宠物禁入"
"No Pets Allowed"?
完美
Perfect.
丹尼斯  快来
Dennis, come on.
你好  欢迎登船
Oh, hello. Welcome aboard.
这是鲍勃
Uh, this is Bob.
说你好  鲍勃  你好  鲍勃
Say hi, Bob. Hi, Bob.
天啦噜  格里芬  我好兴奋耶
Oh, my Gosh, Griffin. I'm like, so excited.
这是我去过最好的酒店了耶
This is like, the nicest hotel I've ever been to.
是呀
Yeah!
这里太好了吧
Man, this is amazing!
有好多项目啊
There's so much to do.
有超大号的游泳池
A living size swimming pool.
任你挑选的自助餐
All you can eat buffet?!
还有全方位spa
Full service spa?!
我要来个海草包扎
Oohho, give me a seaweed rewrap.
哇  听起来跟咱们的旅社一模一样
Wow, it sounds like everything we can do at our hotel?!
但这是在水上
Except on the water!
你成功了宝贝  你爸会喜欢的
You nailed it, honey. Your dad is going to love this.
最好的夏日假期
Best summer vacation ever!
你看到行程之后会更开心的
Wait till you see the itineraries.
真好看
Oh, that's nice.
弗兰克  "火啊  不好"  记得吗
Frank, "Fire, bad" remember?
哦对  但是
Oh, yeah, right, but uh...
也许你也能在游轮上擦出爱的火花
maybe we can find your own fireworks on the cruise, huh?
这又不是《泰坦尼克号》  弗兰克
It's not The Love Boat, Frank.
我是跟家人共度时光的
I'm just here to have fun with my family.
你们好  欢迎登船
Ahoy, there! Welcome aboard.
Bienvenidos.
哇  这是谁
Whoa! Who is that?
我是船长艾瑞卡  没错是人类
I am Captain Ericka, and yes, I'm human.
但不要对我有偏见哦
But don't hold that against me,
非常欢迎你们能够登上
I could not be more excited to have all of you onboard,
史上首个怪兽游轮
our first ever monster cruise!
爸  你还好吗
Dad, are you okay?
哦不  他心脏病犯了
Oh, no. He's having a heart attack!
德古拉  不太像
Drac? Not likely.
唯一能让他犯心脏病的只有木棍
And the only heart attack that can hurt him is with a wooden stake.
一定是中风
It must be a stroke!
其实  我觉得是因为她
Actually, I think it might be her.
先生  手注意着点  我还在这呢
Watch where you're pointing, mister. I'm right here.
你总离我这么近  真吓人
You always stand so close to me. It's creepy.
曾活在黑暗里  但现在不用了
...hiding, living in the shadows, but not anymore.
让我们走出阴影  挥动双手  爪子或触角
You've stood up and waved your hand, a claw or tentacle,
大声欢呼"我们在此  我们多毛  吓人是我们的权利"
and said, "We're here, we are hairy and it is our right to be scary"!
是时候庆祝了
Now, it's time to celebrate.
尽享饕餮盛宴
You'll enjoy gourmet dinings,
令人目眩的探险  不间断的娱乐体验
swirling adventures and nonstop entertainment.
敬候旅程的终点
All awaits to our final destination.
不再迷失的失落之城  亚特兰蒂斯
The lost city that isn't lost anymore, Atlantis!
哇  这群鱼居然是杂技演员  杂技鱼
Whoa, the fish are acrobats. The fishcrobats!
你好  有什么能帮到您的
Hello, how can I help you with?
你一定是独一无二的德古拉了
So, you must be the one and only, Dracula.
真是久仰大名
I have waited so long to meet you.
哇  你真的不会变老  真羡慕你的皮肤
Wow, you really don't age do you? I'd kill for your skin.
你在说特兰西瓦尼亚语吗
Oh, you're speaking Transylvanian.
我一直都很想学
Oh, I always wanted to learn.
真是门浪漫的语言
Oh, such a romantic language.
有口音的男人
You know, there's just something
听起来真是充满智慧
about an accent that makes a man sound so intelligent.
这也是特兰西瓦尼亚语
That's Transylvanian right there,
他在说"很高兴认识你"
he's saying "It's... it's nice to meet you".
那好吧  也很高兴认识你
Oh, well, then. Alibooboo to you as well.
德古拉  德古拉  清醒点
Drac! Drac! Drac, snap out of it!
等等  我一直都想这么做
Wait, wait. I have always wanted to do this, alright?
醒醒  德古拉  清醒点
Wake, up! Wake up, Drac! Snap out of it!
够了
Hey, enough!
兄弟  你没事吧
Hey buddy, you okay?
不  我有事  我有事
No, no, not okay. Not okay.
我  我恋爱了
I... I... I... zinged.
爷我去了摩托店  要买车*
*I went to the Moped store, I said "Sell it".
导购说"您好  您的预算是多少"*
*Salesman's like "What up, what's your budget?"
我实话实说对摩托一窍不通*
*And I'm like "Honestly, I don't know nothing about Mopeds".
他说"我这有个适合您  跟我来"*
*He said "I got the one for you, follow me".
噢  我不敢相信*
*Ooh, it's too real.
镀铬的镜子  我不要挡风玻璃*
*Chromed out mirror, I don't need a windshield.
快瞧瞧呀
Ooh, Check that out.
准备好了
Here we go.
爸爸
Papa!
"儿童乐园"
"Kids Club"?
什么是儿童乐园
What's a kids club?
鱼  没错  亲爱的
Fish. That's right, dear.
我感觉还是没明白
I'm still not sure I understand.
你特意帮我看一整天孩子  鱼
You take my kids all day on purpose? Fish.
没错  有什么不明白的吗
That's right. What's exactly don't you understand?
为啥
Why?
这样他们玩得开心  你也能玩得愉快
So, they can have a great time, and you can have a great time.
鱼
Fish.
不必担心  你今晚就能把它们带走
Oh, don't worry, you'll get them back at the end of the day.
哦好吧  能放一会是一会
Oh, well. That's better than nothing.
我们现在干什么
So... what do we do now?
我们想干什么就干什么
I think... I think we do whatever we want.
什么都行吗
Whatever we want?
什么都行
Whatever we want.
什么都行  什么都行
Whatever we want. Whatever we want.
救我
Help me!
什么都行  什么都行
Whatever we want. Whatever we want.
嗨  你好啊  你们好呀
Oh, hi. Hello. How are you all doin'?
晚上好  船长
Good evening, captain.
你好  天哪
Oh, well, hello. Oh, my goodness.
能不能把  把尾巴抬一下
Would you mind uh... lifting, uh... lifting your tail? You know?
当然没问题
Oh, certainly.
好的  十分感谢
Okay. Thank you so much.
你好啊  欢迎登船
Oh, hello. Welcome aboard.
你说得太对了  曾祖父
Oh, you were so right, greatgrandfather!
怪兽真恶心
Monsters are disgusting!
他们就是动物
They're animals!
我马上到
I'll be right there!
德古拉在船上吗
Dracula, is he onboard?
在  我看见他了
Yes, I saw him.
面对面  我还对他那么友善
Face to face, Ugh! I was so nice to him.
他苍白的面孔  傻头傻脑的笑
That pale face of his, and his goofy smile.
炫耀着他的尖牙
Showing off his fangs.
就跟你说得一样
Ugh! It's just like you taught me.
我说的还算是轻的 他其实更糟糕
He's even worse than I did!
就在那晚  我才意识到
It was that faithful night, that I realize,
人类永远无法战争怪兽
the human could never defeat a monster.
但我不能让家族遗产消失殆尽
But I wouldn't let our family legacy die.
因此我开始寻找答案
And so I began... to search for an answer.
我在一本古书里找到了
And I saw it, in an ancient text.
毁灭乐谱
An instrument of destruction,
强大到可以毁灭整个亚特兰蒂斯的怪兽
so powerful it destroyed Atlantis. A whole city of monsters.
深埋于等待着
And laired deep within new runwood lane, waiting.
无尽的
Endlessly, a service for the lost city.
时过境迁  我的身体每况愈下
Time passed, and my body began to fail me.
如此的可悲  艾瑞卡
Oh, it was so sad, Erica.
先是肝脏再是脾脏
First, my liver then my spleen.
接下来是我的两个肾脏
Followed by a kidney or two.
然后我英俊不再
And my good looks. Oooh!
但我不会被这些打倒
But I wouldn't let that stop me.
我用科技代替了我的器官
I replaced my feeling organs with technology!
再看看现在的我
And look at me now. Mmmhmm.
小姑娘  这可是种改进
Oh, girl, it's an improvement, really.
行吧
Um... sure.
亚特兰蒂斯
120年之后  我终于找到了亚特兰蒂斯
And now after 120 years, I finally found Atlantis.
别管这些了
Oh! Forget about all this!
让我现在就杀了他
Let me get rid of the Dracula right now.
我离他这么的近  可以直接
I was so close to him, I could've just...
不不不
No, no, no, no!
必须按原计划进行
We have to stick to the plan.
将怪兽们引到亚特兰蒂斯
Lure the monsters to Atlantis,
取回毁灭乐谱
retrieve the instrument of destruction.
把它们困住  再将其冲走
Trap them there, and then flush them out.
现在是暂时的
It's temporary.
答应我  你不会试图去杀德古拉
Now, promise me. You won't try and kill Dracula.
好吧  我保证
Ugh, fine! I promise!
保证什么
Promise word.
我保证不会试图去杀德古拉  行吗
I promise I wouldn't try and kill Dracula. Okay?
清醒/休息
别担心  曾祖父  我不会试图去杀他
Don't worry, greatgrandfather, I won't try and kill him...
我会杀掉他
I will kill him!
Tonight
I just want to take you higher
put yo' pinky rings up to the moon
Girls, what y'all trying to do?
24 karat magic in the air
Head to toe so player
Uh, look out!
信号枪
专备急用
Pop pop, it's show time (Show time)
Show time (Show time)
Guess who's back again?
Oh they don't know? (Go on tell 'em)
I bet they know soon as we walk in (Showin' up)
Wearing Cuban links (ya)
Designer minks (ya)
Inglewood's finest shoes (Whoop, whoop)
Don't look too hard
Might hurt ya'self
Known to give the color red the blues
Girls, what y'all trying to do?
24 karat magic in the air
Head to toe so player
Just put your pinky rings up to the moon
靠  妈的
Oh! Darn it.
Girls, what y'all trying to do?
24 karat magic in the air
Head to toe so player
Put your pinky rings up to the moon
Girls, what y'all trying to do?
不错哦  德古拉
Work it, Dracula.
24 karat magic in the air
你懂得
You know it.
看着不错哦  德古拉
Oh, looking good, Drac.
感觉也不错  弗兰克
Feeling good, Frank.
看看你啊  这么花哨
Look at you, so fancy.
啥  这个吗  拜托
What? This? Please.
噢  这是要衣装取悦？
Ooh, dress to impress, huh?
取悦  我需要取悦谁啊
Impress? Oh, who do I need to impress?
那是船长艾瑞卡吗
Hey, is that Captain Ericka?
哦不不不
Oh no, no, no, no!
哎呀  不是她
Oops. No, not her.
太好笑啦
Ooh, that's great!
真好笑
Very amusing.
抱歉德古拉  只是
Sorry, Drac. You know, it's just...
我们从没见过你这样子
we've never seen you like this.
我知道  这根本说不通
I know, I know. It doesn't make any sense.
你不能有两次真爱  简直不可能
You can't zing twice. It's impossible!
但我却爱上她了  所以现在我
But I did, so now I...
梅维斯怎么办
But what about, Mavis?
她想让你开心  不是吗
She wants you to be happy, right?
我相信她会顺其自然的
I'm sure she'll go with the flow.
不不  梅维斯需要我  我是她的依靠
Oh, no, no, no! Mavis needs me, she depends on me.
我要回家  和她在一起
I need to be home with my family.
虽然默里才是来自埃及
Hey, Murray here may be from Egypt,
但你才是一直不敢面对现实的人
but you're the one in denial.
你们get到梗没
You guys get that?
你这巴掌直接扇我   梅维斯
Ow! You hit me right in the... Mavis!
什么也不许说  不然我做鬼也不放过你
Don't say a word, or I'll hunt your dreams.
玩得开心吗
Having fun?
有你在这里  我会更开心
Oh, I'm having even more fun, now that you're here.
爸爸  我很开心能跟你一起出来玩
You know, dad, I feel really lucky to have this time with you.
我们所有人一起真的很特别
All of us together, it's really special.
我也这么觉得  小蛛猴
Me too, spider monkey.
准备好跟我玩怪兽球了吗
Now, are you ready for me to destroy you in monster ball?
怪兽球
Whoohoo! Monster ball!
快来啊  祖父
Come on, Papa Drac!
来吧  我可是游戏之王
Oh, do bring it on! For I am king of family fun!
好了  谁准备好被扁了
Alright! Who is ready to get pubbled?
我可警告你  我以前待过
I gotta warn you, I've played
圣克鲁斯大学的排球校内第二代表队
second team coed Intramural volleyball at Santa Cruz.
行吧哥们  随你怎么说
Sure, pal. Whatever you say.
大家伙  拜托  注意发型  注意发型
Everybody, just please, watch the hair. Watch the hair!
来吧  开始吧
Oh, let's go! Let's do this!
天哪  这会很有趣的
Oh, my gosh! This is gonna be so much fun.
准备好  你要挨揍啦
Be ready! Here comes the pain!
注意发型  发型
Not the hair! Not the hair!
不不不
No, no, no, no, no...
太好啦
Oh, yes!
艾瑞卡船长  请立刻去甲板
Captain Ericka, you are needed on deck.
下一站再见  德古拉
Next stop. Byebye, Dracula.
好勒  宝贝
Okay, baby!
这个我来
Oh, baby. I got this.
哈喽怪兽们
Hey there, monsters.
耶  我说啥了
Yeah! What I'd say?!
我们抵达了第一站
We're arriving at our first destination.
水下火山
The under water volcano!
所有人  拿起你的潜水装备
Everyone, grab your scuba gear and
准备好探索水下奇迹吧
get ready to explore the wonders of the sea.
尤其是你  德古拉伯爵
Especially you. Count Dracula.
看见没  她喜欢你
You see that now? She likes you.
哦不不不
Oh, no, no, no, no...
That sounds like a zing in full effect.
不不不
Oh, no, no, no, no, no...
真的真的真的
Oh, yes, yes, yes, yes...
我只是来
I'm just here to have family fun. Family, family, fun, fun.
大概就在这
Oh, yes, right about here...
各位  这边请
Right this way, everyone.
欢迎来到水下王国的奇观之一
Welcome to one of the true wonders of the under watered kingdom.
火地岛火山
I give you, Volcano Del Fuego!
当地海生物称之为
Or as the local sea life call it...
多可爱的一家人啊
Oh, what a cute family.
什么  不对  德古拉不好  不好
What? No, it's not! Dracula, bad! Dracula, bad!
弗兰克  刚吃完饭你怎么又饿了
Frank, we just ate. I can't believe you're hungry already.
抱歉  你知道的  就是
I'm sorry. You know what it is... it's all just...
看到那么多海鲜到处游走
All that seafood, just swimming around it.
我一看到食物
When I say food.
天哪
Oh, man!
德古拉  德古拉  德古拉
Oh, Dracula, Dracula, Dracula, Dracula, Dracula!
我离得这么近  他就像在戏弄我
I get so close, it's almost like he's teasing me.
我真是受不了了  我必须要得到他
I just... I can't stand it anymore! I have to get him!
天哪  那个水下火山真是热
Boy, that under water volcano was hot!
你好  鲍勃
Oh. Hi, Bob.
哥们  我答应过你会玩乒乓球是吧
Buddy, we promised you we'd play... uh... pingpong now?
丹尼斯  它是谁
Um, Dennis, who is this?
我朋友鲍勃  说你好  鲍勃
Uh... it's our friend, Bob. Say hi, Bob.
你好  鲍勃
Hi, Bob.
好啦  该玩乒乓球了
Okay! Time to go play pingpong.
德古拉  德古拉  德古拉
Drac! Drac! Drac! Drac! Drac! Drac!
兄弟们  哪起火了啊
Hey, boys, where's the fire?
格里芬他
Oh, uh! Well, Griffin here,
他有话跟你说
he... he has something to tell you.
我说吗
Me?
哦对  我手被咬了  自从那个时候
Uh... oh! Yeah, I got this bite on my hand, and since you know...
你是叮咬专家  我想你能给我
gee... you're a biting expert, I thought you could take me...
是啊  快过来  这边灯光亮
Yeah, come on over here! The light is there...
好吧
Okay...
到底怎么回事  你们比平时更奇怪
Okay, what is going on? You guys are acting weirder than normal.
你猜我们刚才听到了什么
You are not gonna believe what we heard but...
嘘  我说了不想让梅维斯伤心
Shh! I told you I don't want to upset Mavis.
但你们到底在说啥
But, what are you talking about?!
好吧  就是弗兰克饿了
Okay, well see, Frank on hungry so, no surprise there, but uh...
我们游回船上  听见艾瑞卡疯狂地叫你名字
We swam back the ship, and we found Ericka, raving about you!
她离不开你  哥们  正经地
She can't live without you, buddy. It's serious!
德古拉  这样太好了
So, Drac, this is great. Now,
你想不想让她跟你一起同居
are you gonna make her move on your coffin or what?
也许吧
Ah, yes. Maybe?
不不  已经过去好久了  我都不知道怎么做
No, no... it's been a while, I don't even know, where to start.
很简单  德古拉
It's easy, Drac. Make some small talk.
记得要微笑
And remember to smile.
看向她的双眼  施展你的魅力
Look into her eyes. Jimmy Cash her.
开开玩笑  问问她的部位都是哪的
Say something funny. Ask her where her parts are from.
夸夸她的包扎  你喜欢棺材
Oh, and say that her wrappings look nice. You like coffins.
称赞"她的脖子很美味"
Compliment her. "Your neck looks delicous"
她来了
Here she comes.
好了德古拉  去吧
Okay, Drac. Hit it.
你美味的脖子包扎在一个好棺材里
Your delicous neck wrappings are in a nice coffin.
你想看我的部位吗
Would you like to see my parts?
好呀  我愿意跟你约会
Yes, I'd love to go out with you.
什么  什么
What? What?!
午夜餐厅见  别迟到哦
Canteena, midnight. Don't be late.
真够悬的
Phew! That was a close one.
等等  叮叮  回来
Wait! Tinkles, come back!
住手  叮叮  停下来
Stop it, Tinkles! Stop!
叮叮  停住  等等
Tinkles, stop! Wait!
快走快走
Move, move, move...
叮叮  停下来
Tinkles, stop!
我被发现了
I've been found!
你永远也别想抓到我  怪兽
You'll never get me, monster!
嘘  叮叮  住手  嘘
Shh! Tinkles, stop! Shh! Shh!
呕
Ew...
各位  我们即将
Everybody, we are pulling
抵达下一站  荒岛
up to our next stop. The deserted island.
是时候在沙滩上迷惘了
It's time to get lost on the beach.
希望你在这期间
And we hope you, a time in yourselves.
放松身心 玩的开心
Some fun and relaxation.
沙滩时间
Whoohoo! Beach time!
强尼  你去准备东西
Johnny, you go set everything up.
爸  你去排队买冰淇淋
And, dad, you go get in line for the snow cones.
其实  我在想
You know, actually, I was thinking,
你和查理应该独处一会
You and Charlie should spend some time together.
你怎么叫的来着  约会之夜
What do you call it again? Eh... date night?
约会之夜
Date night?!
那你干嘛
What are you gonna do?
我想和兄弟们
Well, I thought me and the guys,
借这个机会多陪陪丹尼斯
would take this oppurtunity to spend some quality time with Dennis.
哦好吧  好主意
Oh, okay. That's a great idea.
走吧强尼  约会之夜
Come on, Johnny. Date night.
约约约会
Dadadadate night!
好了  去吧
Okay, here you go!
好宝贝  这回我来
Good girl! I got this one.
什么声音  听起来像咱孩子
What was that? It sounds like our children.
真是咱孩子  快跑
It is our children! Run!
弗兰克  能不能帮我抹点防晒霜
Frank, would you rub some moonscreen on my back,
不然我会晒伤的
before I get burned?
稍等宝贝  孩子们把我埋土里了
Wait one second, honey. II... the kids buried me in the sand.
谢了宝贝
Mmm. Thanks, honey.
这里是不是很棒
Isn't this place amazing?
哇  菜单居然在瓶子里
Whoa, the menu is in the bottle!
真聪明  是不是很棒宝贝
Genius! Isn't that awesome, honey?
什么  哦抱歉  我在想爸爸
What? Oh, Sorry. I was just thinking about my dad.
有没有觉得他最近很奇怪
Don't you think he's acting weird lately?
没觉得啊  除了暗恋船长之外
Not really. Besides having a huge crush on the Captain.
什么  没错
What? Oh, yeah. The love boat,
暗恋绝逼能让人疯狂
is definitely making another run.
不可能  他是我爸
No way, he's... he's my dad.
我知道  很奇怪对吧
I know, right? It's weird.
我爸妈亲亲的时候  我还是会闭眼睛
When my parents kiss, I still close my eyes.
我确实从没想过  他会跟别人在一起
I guess, I never thought about him with anyone besides my mom.
你不介意的  对吗
You're cool with it though, right?
当然  我希望他开心
Of course, I want him to be happy.
绝对的
Totally.
Totally...
晚安  我的朋友
Good evening, my friend.
有没有  饮品
Have you, eh... beverage?
快来救命
To quench me of my, bargement.
吸食山羊血的怪物
当然有  卓柏卡布拉先生
Yes, of course, Mr. Chupacabra.
十分感谢
Thank you very much.
你真美
You look ravishing.
哦谢谢  我只是
Oh, um... thank you. I was just...
所以那个  你姓什么
So, um... does Captain Ericka have a last name?
嗯 哦
Uh... Uh.. Oh, uh...
鳄梨酱
Oh, Guacamolle!
艾瑞卡鳄梨酱  听起来很  国际化
Ericka Guacamolle? That's so... international.
不是啦  我们来吃鳄梨酱
No! Guacamolle for us to share.
今晚的满月可真美
Oh, how beautiful is that full moon tonight.
看  就在你身后
Look, right behind you.
浓缩大蒜油
这里的食物好吃死了
Mmm. The food here is to die for.
天啦噜  这鳄梨酱可真多
Holy moly, that was a lot of Guacamolle.
你还好吗
Are you feeling all right?
挺好啊  怎么了
Totally fine. Why?
没什么
No reason.
鳄梨酱里一定放了大蒜
Ugh, there must have been a garlic in the Guacamolle.
哦不  是不是会致命啊
Oh no. Isn't that deadly for you?
不不不  只是我
No, no, no... it's just that I...
大蒜不耐受
garlic intolerant!
你放的吗
Was that you?
哦耶  海豚冲浪
Oh, yeah! Dolphin surfing!
妈妈爸爸好  你们好
Hi, mama. Hi, papa. Hi, guys.
你好
Oh, hey there!
嘿 再见
Adios! Hey.
我爸是不是也在里面
Isn't my dad in there too?
别担心  我就在这
Don't worry, I'm over here. Blah, blah, blah.
不  祖父不在这里  他去约会了
No, Papa Drac's not here, he's on his date.
约会
Date?
请原谅  我太紧张了
Please forgive me. I... I'm just very nervous.
我妻子死后  就没约会过
You see... I haven't had a date since... my wife died.
那时你女儿多大
How old was your daughter?
她还是个婴儿  当单身父亲很难
She was just an infant. It was hard being a single dad,
但我尽力了
but I... I did my best.
我也从没见过妈妈和爸爸
I never knew my mother either... or my father.
我很遗憾
Oh, I'm so sorry.
谁抚养你长大的  我的曾祖父
Who raised you? My greatgrandfather.
我基本是在这艘船上长大的
I basically grew up on this ship.
所以你是船长
That's why you're a captain.
是啊  我只知道这些
Yeah, it's all I've ever known.
嗯 很难  解析  家事 你懂的
And it's just... expected. You know, a family thing.
我明白  家庭重于一切
I understand, family is everything.
你必须尊重过去  但也要创造自己的未来
You have to honor the past. But we make our own future.
爸  梅维斯
Dad? Mavis?!
强尼
Johnny!
我和艾瑞卡船长在
Captain Ericka and I, were just...
讨论酒店产业
discussing the hospitality industry, you know.
我的天 你们居然还在讨论工作！
Drac workscout! You're working now?
这本该是个假期  家庭旅行
This is supposed to be a vacation. A family vacation.
我该去做船长的事了
II should really go... do captainy things.
爸  你说要陪陪丹尼斯的
Dad, you said you were gonna spend time with Dennis?
丹尼斯  丹尼斯  丹尼斯
Dennis? Dennis? Dennis! Dennis?
你说得对  他去哪了
Oh, yeah, you're right. Where is that kid?
丹尼索维奇  你应该跟紧我的
Dennisovich? You're supposed to be with me.
快点丹尼斯  现在是家庭时间  别藏了
Come on now, kid. It's family time. Quit hiding, Dennis!
刚才什么情况
What was that about?
你爸的约会吗
You mean your dad's date?
那不是约会  只是在谈工作
It wasn't a date. It was... work stuff.
我跟你说  强尼
I'm telling you, Johnny,
我不太信任那个女人
there is something about that woman I don't trust.
但你希望爸能开心  不是吗
But you want your dad to be happy, right?
没错  但不是跟她一起
Yes. Just... not with her.
小心哦宝贝  这个鳄梨酱里全是大蒜
Whoo! Heads up, honey, this Guac is loaded with garlic.
大蒜
Garlic?
你放屁都这么可爱  宝贝
Aww, that's a cute tune, honey.
我们彻夜未眠  咱再
We've been up all night! Let's stay up all day too!
嗨起来
Let's get wild.
艾瑞卡
Ericka!
怎么了
Ahh! Huh! What?
你去哪了  小姑娘
Just where have you been, young lady?
工作啊  穿这身吗
Uh.. doing the work? Wearing that?
你跟他在一起  我知道
You were with him. I know it!
跟谁  谁  你知道是谁
Who? Who? You know who!
你一直在背着我
You've been sneaking around my back,
想去杀了德古拉  对不对
trying to kill Dracula again, haven't you?
是又怎样  我是个成年人
So, what if I have? I am a grown woman!
我想杀谁就杀谁
I have the right to kill whoever I want.
事关重大  你会毁了遗产的
It's not just about you. You could've ruin the legacy.
万一他发现你是谁了怎么办
What if he discovered who you were?
我知道  我脑子没转弯
I know, I know, I wasn't thinking.
但他身上  就有一种魔力
There's just... there's just something about him,
让我疯狂
That just drives me crazy!
我看见他就想要
I just... I see him and I want to...
揍他  应该吧
Punch him. Uh, I guess.
我已经等不及了
I can't wait to get this over with.
别担心  用不了多久了
Don't worry. It won't be long now.
只要你拿到毁灭乐曲
Once you recovered the instrument of destruction,
我们就所向披靡
no one can stop us.
德古拉都不是对手
Not even Dracula!
打扰了  间谍
Excuse me! Spy!
快动手  趁没人发现
Now, quickly, before someone comes!
各位请到甲板上集合
Everyone assemble on the floor with deck.
我们即将抵达终点
We are arriving at our final destination.
世界的最深渊
From the depths of creation,
伟大的城市再次崛起
the mighty city has risen once again.
有史以来最伟大的怪兽文明之地
Home to the greatest monster civilization the world has ever known.
远超雅典与罗马的
Far surpassing Athens and Rome,
艺术文明及哲学思想
and arts culture and sophistication.
请看传奇的失落之城亚特兰蒂斯
I give you the legendary lost city of... Atlantis.
北欧神话中的巨型海怪
欢迎来到亚特兰蒂斯
Welcome to Atlantis!
现在是玩乐时光！
我好兴奋啊
Ooh, I am so excited. Oh, Kentucky!
红数赢了
Going in red.
你想得美
Oh, no, you don't.
上次你就输了个胳膊和腿
Last time you gambled, you lost an arm and a leg.
别生气
Don't raise your voice...
不准赌博
So, no gamble!
好的 没问题  不赌博
Frank! Yes, you got it. No gambling!
叮叮  停下
Tinkles, stop, wait!
停下来  叮叮  等等
Stop it, Tinkles! Wait!
看到梅维斯了吗  我必须要找到她
Have you guys seen Mavis? I have to find her!
为什么  怎么了
Why? What's going on?
我要把艾瑞卡的事告诉她
I'm going to tell her about Ericka!
我不能再骗自己的女儿了
I can't lie to my own daughter anymore.
她是这世界上最重要的人
She is the most important person in the world to me.
我必须告诉她真相
I have to tell her the truth.
等我先跟艾瑞卡谈完
Right after I talk to Ericka.
喂
Hey!
好了  我全  弗兰克
All right, I'm all... Frank?
你确定要这么做吗
Are you sure you know what you're doing?
没问题  我全押
I got this. I'm all in.
强尼  看见我爸了吗  没准他跟鲍勃在一起
Johnny, have you seen my dad? Maybe he's with Bob.
他为什么会跟鲍勃在一起  鲍勃挺不错啊
Why would he be with Bob? Bob's a great guy.
哦  他在那  谁  鲍勃吗
Oh, there he is. Who, Bob?
小心
施工中
你在这啊  鲍勃
There he is. Hi, Bob!
就是这个
There it is!
你救了我  当然  为什么不救
You saved my life. Of course. Why wouldn't I?
我只是  不敢相信你会救人类
I just... I can't believe you would do that for a human.
人类  怪兽  有什么区别呢
Humans? Monsters? What's the difference?
没错  没错
Yeah, right... right.
等等  你在这干什么
Wait, what, uh... what are you doing here?
我就是  吸血鬼能预测未来  所以
Oh, I, well, you know, Vampires can predict the future, so...
我知道你需要我帮忙
I know you would need my help.
是吗  从没听说过
Huh? Never heard that before.
真的真的  大家都知道
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah. It's a well known fact.
那  你在这干什么
Well, eh... What are you doing here?
哦  我来这取它
Oh, yeah, uh... I'm here to get that.
它是我的传家宝
Yeah, it's a family heirloom.
丢在海里了
Yeah, it was lost at... at sea,
我曾祖父弄丢了
and um, my greatgrandfather has lost, once...
完全着了迷  得拿回来  所以
Uh, totally obsessed with. Gotta get it back. So, anyhoo...
谢谢救了我  但剩下的我能行
Thanks for saving my life. But um, I can take it from here.
得更小心点
Gotta be a little more careful.
不然你能救我几次呢  是吧
How many times can you save my life, right?
不知道  每一次吧
I don't know. Every time?
真的吗  那么
Really? Well, then...
哇
Wow!
刚才太棒了
Oh! That was incredible.
不去拿你的传家宝了吗
Oh, uh, don't you want to get your family heirloom thingy?
哦对
Oh, right.
拿到了
Got it.
哦  我来帮你拿掉
Oh, let me get that for you.
爸  梅维斯
Dad! Mavis?
你在对我爸干什么
What are you doing to my father?
梅维斯住手  放她下来
Mavis, stop! Put her down.
不  她想伤你  你看不出来吗
No, she's trying to hurt you. Why can't you see that?
因为我  因为我恋爱了
Because I... because... because I zinged...
什么  我爱上了艾瑞卡
What? I zinged... with Ericka!
不  这不可能
No, that can't be true.
真爱只有一次  我也这么以为的
You only zing once. That's what I thought too.
真爱  什么真爱
Zing? What's a zing?
哦  算是怪兽的
Oh, well, it's a thing... for monsters.
有点像是一见钟情
It's kind of like our love at first sight.
什么  不不不  你都不了解我
What? No. No, no, no. You don't even know me.
是还没有  但我们会
Well, not yet, but we'll just...
不  你不明白
No, no, you don't understand...
我不能与你一起  永远都不能与你这样的人一起
I can't be with you, I could... never be with someone like you.
永远都不能与怪兽一起
I could never be with... a monster.
爸  我很遗憾
Dad, I'm so sorry.
我  没关系
I... It doesn't matter.
你听到她说的了
You heard what she said.
但真爱是不会说谎的
But a zing never lies.
你拿到了
Ah, you got it!
是啊
Yes!
现在我们有了毁灭乐谱
Now that we have the instrument of destruction.
家族的遗产得以传承了
Our family legacy will be fulfilled.
但首先  得引他们去参加舞会
But first, we'll draw them in with a dance party.
我喜欢跳舞
I love to dance.
弗兰克  能帮我拉上吗  我们要迟到了
Frank, could you zip that up? We're gonna be late.
你从哪整来的
Where did you get those?
我  我把手输没了
Uh, see I guess I... Eh... I lost my hands...
赌输的  但没关系
Gambling, but... No big deal.
看  我有这个啊  还很新
Look, I've got these. For the sake of new...
看呀  喀哒  喀哒
Look at this. Clap, clap, click, click.
我挺喜欢的  真的
II kinda like 'em. I like 'em.
看来派对在这边
Ah! I guess the party's this way.
让我们开始狂欢吧
Let's get them party started right!
哈
Huh?
不是说派对在这边吗
I thought they said the party was this way.
DJ在蛤蜊壳里
DJ in a clam shell?
羡慕嫉妒恨
I'm so jealous.
不敢相信我爸
I can't believe my dad
爱上了一个想杀他的人
zinged with someone who's trying to kill him.
是啊  真爱让人痴狂
Yep, zing makes you do crazy things.
搞笑呢  强尼
Really, Johnny?
最需要领悟的就是
What's most important to understand...
爱情之谜
is that love is an infinite
难以破解
enigma that is beyond our understanding.
你我二人  世界之隔
You and I have were two halves. A world apart.
但随之我们沿着命运之链
But then, we followed the strand of destiny,
找到彼此  合二为一
and were brought together and now has made one whole.
但如果他和她
But what if she and he...
你须释放消极之气  探索内心
You must release all the negativity, and look within.
纽带之结  牢不可破
For bond is unbreakable.
你说得对宝贝  哇谢了
You're right, honey. Wow... thanks.
哇  你听起来超聪明的  爸
Whoa, you sounded pretty smart, dad.
是吗
Oh, that?
那只是我
That was just the velocity of secret zing
功夫少林僧大师
Kungfu Shaolin Monk Master.
总之  咱接着跳舞吧
Anyways, let's get back to dancing.
好呀
Cool.
爸  你必须跟艾瑞卡谈谈  什么
Dad? You have to talk to Ericka. What?
我知道我说了什么  但
I know. I know what I said before, but...
也许我反应有一点点过了
maybe I over reacted a teensy bit.
只是一想到要失去你
It's just the thought of losing you.
什么  你说什么呢  失去我吗
What? What are you talking about? Losing me?
很明显  你结婚之后
Well, obviously after you get married,
肯定会住在船上  环游世界
you're gonna live on the ship, and travel around the world.
停停停  放松  梅维斯
Whoa, whoa, whoa... Slow down, Mavis.
我向你保证两件事
There are two things I can promise you.
第一  谁也不能让我离开你和大家
One, nothing can ever take me from you and all my family.
第二  我是不会住在船上的
Two, I will never live on a boat.
你是我的宝贝小狼蛛  我怎能离开你呢
You're my cute little tarantula! How can I ever leave you?
爸  正经的  去找她
Dad, seriously? Go talk to her.
我不能  你听见她的话了
I can't. You heard what she said.
她永远都不能与我这样的人在一起
She could never be with someone like me.
不  爸  你只是一半
No, dad. You're just a half
而你必须要遵从命运找到  无限整体
and you have to follow your destiny to find it. Infinite whole.
听起来像强尼说的
You sound like Johnny.
重点是你不能否认真爱
Point is, you can't deny a zing.
怪兽  人类还是独角兽  都不重要
Monster? Human? Unicorn? It doesn't matter.
去找她  快
So, go to her. Now!
好吧  这就去
Okay. I'm on it.
哥们  你不能上来
Hey man, you're not allowed up here.
DJ台可是很神圣的
The DJ booth is a sacred space...
不要  叮叮  安静
No, no, no, Tinkles! Quiet, quiet!
这是谁
Who is this?
我就知道你记得我  你的死敌
Heh! I know you recognize me. Your greatest rival.
哦对  你是机场旅游入境的那个人
Hmm? Oh, right! You're on that holiday inbound by the airport.
不  是我  亚伯拉罕・范・海辛
No! It is I! Abraham Van Helsing.
范・海辛  这么多年过去了
Van Helsing? After all this years.
你看起来糟透了
You look... awful.
我的天啊  你们还在办公？
Well, who always redicrocent self.
额  这个对你有帮助  干翻所有怪物
Well, this will serve you out! And all monsters!
啥  那不是艾瑞卡的传家宝吗
Eh... Huh? That's just Ericka's family heirloom thingy.
做得好
Good, Malericka.
艾瑞卡
Ericka?
你个蠢货  她不仅是这艘船的船长
You fool, not only is she the ships captain,
但她也是
but she also happens to be...
不  你告诉他
Wait, you tell him.
我是他的曾孙女
I'm his greatgranddaughter.
我是艾瑞卡・范・海辛
I'm Ericka Van Helsing.
我就知道她有问题
I knew there was something wrong with her.
但  我
But... I...
发生了什么  我
...see what happened... I...
现在都知根知底了  回到死亡的话题吧
Well, now that we're all caught up. Let's get back to the dying.
请看  灭绝怪兽的秘诀
Behold, the key to the demise of all monsters.
让我看看  这和那
Uh... let's see, right and then...
聆听毁灭你们的旋律吧
Listen to the melody of your destruction.
哦  没想到这么好听
Ooh, I didn't know it'd be that good.
快看  是北海巨妖
Hey, look! It's the Kraken...
大家快逃
Everybody out, now!
我们被困住了  大家往回撤
We're trapped! Everybody get back!
必须及时阻止
This has to stop now!
德古拉  不
Drac, no!
爸
Dad!
梅维斯
Mavis!
德古拉的死期到了
Time for the immortal Dracula to die.
爸
Dad!
不
No!
艾瑞卡
Ericka!
鲍勃  快帮忙
Bob! Help!
叮叮  丹尼斯
Tinkles?! Dennis?
哦不  鲍勃居然是叮叮  它怎么来的呀
Um, no. Bob is Tinkles? How did he get here?
但幸亏它来了  快看
But thank goodness he did. 'Cause look!
你不能这么做  你冤枉他们了
You can't do this, you're wrong about monsters!
德古拉救过我
Dracula, he saved my life.
什么
What?!
对不起德古拉  我一直想要杀了你
I'm so sorry, Drac. I was trying to kill you this whole time.
但我意识到自己有多错误
But then I realize how wrong I was.
这一切有多错误
How wrong all of this is.
然后我
And then I...
我恋爱了
I zinged.
恋爱  什么鬼
Zinged? What's a zing?
是怪兽的爱  你不会懂的
It's a monster thing. You wouldn't understand.
就像是真爱
It's like true love.
爱
Love?
好吧  看来遗产在我这里终结
Well, I guess the legacy ends with me.
真是个尴尬的结局
That's an awkward ending.
不  是时候开启新的遗产了
Nope! It's time to start a new legacy.
怪兽人类共同的遗产
A monsterhuman legacy.
不
No!
德古拉
Drac!
范・海辛的音乐正控制那个大章鱼
Van Helsing's beat are controlling the giant octopus thingy.
这世上我最讨厌的就是邪恶的DJ
If there's one thing I hate, it's an evil DJ.
开始
Bringing...
正能量
Positive energy.
准备好DJ大战吧
Get ready for a DJ battle!
你随身带着这些玩意儿吗
You just carry all that stuff around with you?
一日为DJ  终日为DJ
Once a bar mitzvah DJ, always a bar mitzvah DJ.
我们用好的音乐  打败邪恶的音乐
We're gonna use good music, to defeat his evil music.
什么  相信我  我懂音调
What? Trust me, I know the tunes,
但力量在你手上
but you've got the power.
好的  好了  开场曲是
Alright. Okay. Opening song is me off the shezack!
哦好了  放这个
Ooh, got it! Play this.
这噪音哪来的
What is that noise?
我喜欢这首歌  感觉不错
Whoa, I like this one. This feels good.
你个蠢货
You fool!
他的音乐太强大了
Oh! His music is too powerful.
我们需要更积极一点的音乐
We're gonna need something even more positive.
就现在  德古拉
Now, Drac!
真的吗
Really?
传达的信息是好的
It has a nice message.
我真是受够了
I've had enough with this nonsense!
强尼  我们需要
Johnny, we need the most brain
一种在整个宇宙的历史上最具统治力的音调来打败它
dominating tone happening in this song thingy,in the history of all the universe!
快点快点  在哪里在哪里
Come on, come on, come on... Where is it, where is it...
快点  我不知道
Hurry up! I do not know!
选择太多了
There's too many choices!
不  等等
No, wait!
就这个
This... is... it!
搞什么
What the?
天哪  真够臭的
Boy, that stinks.
起作用了
It's working.
强尼过时的音乐正在打败邪恶音乐
Hey, Johnny's corny music is defeating the evil music.
我还挺喜欢
I kinda like it.
不
No!
这音乐太魔性了
I'm a slave to this rhythm!
不要
No!
德古拉  你在干什么
Drac, what are you doing?
一定要比它们强大
Gotta be greater than the haters.
为什么
Why?
为什么经历过这一切  你还会救我
Why after everything would you save my life?
因为本质上  我们都一样
Because basically, we are all the same.
爪子还是双手  两只眼还是三只眼
Claws or hands, two eyes or three eyes.
绿皮肤  还是没皮肤
Green skin. No skin.
智慧超凡
Prickly. Brainy.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
你真棒
You are amazing.
看着我  丹尼斯
Look at me, Dennis.
看着我
Look at me.
拜托  你
Come on, you can't deny it.
不  我还太小不能恋爱
No, I'm too young to zing.
我感觉好愚蠢
I feel kind of silly now.
这些年来  我一直在追捕处决你们
For decades, I have hunted your kind...or executed you.
我唯一能补偿你们的就是
The only thing I can do to make it up to you is...
给你们退30%的钱
Give you... eh... a 30% refund.
不可能  太可笑了
Oh, hell no! That's preposterous!
好吧
Oh, alright.
全额退款
Full refund.
韦恩  婉达  你们俩怎么了
Wayne, Wanda. What happened to you guys?
对啊  都没怎么见过你俩
Yeah. We like, hardly saw you on the cruise.
我知道
Yeah, I know.
我们被打了镇定剂  大部分时间被锁在了衣柜里
We got tranquilized and spent most of the trip locked in a closet.
我们打算放假再去一次
We're gonna book it again for the holidays.
你好  办理入住吗  没错  谢谢
Hi! Checking in? Yes. Thank you.
好的  房间已经准备好了
Great, I have a room all ready for you.
哥们  你介不介意
Hey, buddy, would you mind...
没问题兄弟
Sure, thing pal.
好了好了  到底怎么了
Okay. Okay, what's going on, Sneakypants?
没什么
Oh, nothing.
只是  我不想让任何人打扰我们
It's just, I wanted to make sure nobody would bother us.
为什么
Oh, why?
你是要吸我的血吗
Are you going to suck up my blood, Blah, blah, blah?
不是啦
No.
我是想问你
I was going to ask you if...
愿意嫁给我吗
you would marry me?
你意下如何
Well, what do you say?
你愿意嫁给我吗
Will you marry me?
我  我
I... I...
啥
Huh?...
我是说  我
I mean... I would...
她说什么
What's she saying?
我也不确定
Uh... I'm not sure.
我愿意
Yes!
END